const cardInfo = [
  {
    question: "What is Cloud Computing ?",
    answer:
      "Cloud computing is the practice of using a network of remote servers hosted on the internet to store, manage and process data, rather than a local server or a personal computer ",
  },
  {
    question: "What is On-Premise?",
    answer:
      "You own the servers, hire the IT people, pay or rent the real estate, and take all the risk",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Cloud Providers",
    answer:
      "Someone else owns the servers, hires the It people, pays for the real estate. You are responsible for configuring cloud services and code, someone else takes care of the rest",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the different types of cloud computing",
    answer: "SaaS, PaaS, IaaS",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Saas ?",
    answer:
      "Software as a service, a completed product that is run and managed by the service provider. Like gmail",
  },
  {
    question: "What is PasS ?",
    answer:
      "A Platform as a service removes the need for your organization to manage the underlying infrastructure. Focus on deployment and management of your application. Like heroku",
  },
  {
    question: "IaaS ?",
    answer:
      "Infrastructure as a serivce. The basic building blocks for cloud IT. Provides access to networking features, computers, and data storage space. Like AWS",
  },
  {
    question: "What is an AZ ?",
    answer: "Availability zone",
  },
  {
    question: "How many AZ are there in total ?",
    answer: "80",
  },
  {
    question: "How many geographic regions?",
    answer: "25",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the latency between AZ'z ?",
    answer: "<10 ms",
  },
  {
    question: "What is an edge location?",
    answer:
      "A datacenter owned by a trusted partner of AWS which has a direct connection to the AWS network. Allows low latency no matter where the end user is geographically. Outnumber AZ",
  },
  {
    question: "What is GovCloud Regions?",
    answer:
      "Allow customers to host sensitive Controlled Unclassified Information and other types of regulated workloads. Only operated by employees who are US citizens on US soil",
  },
  {
    question: "What does ELB stand for?",
    answer: "Elastic Load Balancer",
  },
  {
    question: "What does ELB do ?",
    answer:
      "Automatically distributes incoming application traffic and scales resources to meet traffic demands",
  },
  {
    question: "What is an Amazon EC2 Instance Storage",
    answer: "Temporary block storage",
  },
  {
    question: "What is S3? ",
    answer:
      "Infinitely scaling storage. Allows people to store objects (files) in buckets (directories)",
  },
  {
    question: "Is S3 a global or regional service?",
    answer: "Global, but buckets are created in a region",
  },
  {
    question: " What is an S3 Object key?",
    answer: "the full path",
  },
  {
    question: "What is max size of an S3 object?",
    answer: "5TB (5000GB)",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Encryption S3 Security?",
    answer: "Encrypt objects in Amazon S3 using encryption keys",
  },
];

export default cardInfo;
